Christopher Brown

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Hello there, I go by Chris. I have been a frontend developer for almost two years. I'm interested in all things related to development, frontend to backend. Currently learning more about Gatsby JS with GraphQL. I have a deep passion for learning and solving problems but a deeper passion for helping others learn.

LOCATION

Address

- Clarksville, Tn
- Cbrowndev88@gmail.com
- 270-804-6730
- o chrisbrowndeveloper.com
- in chris-brown-48477b1bb
- ChrisB32-cloud

WORK EXPERIENCE

THE BURGER STORE

WEB DEVELOPER | THEBURGERSTORENASHVILLE.COM

Feb 2021-Present

- Designed & built a full-stack website with mobile first approach that allows the user/admin to have areas of the site with integrated contact forms. Site feature public and private routing, context API, and authentication.
- The goal was have a solution for the company where the user/admin can update and change menu items frequently with image uploads and descriptions, menu is dynamically generated.
- Technology: Next.JS, React, Context API, Sass, Bootstrap, noSQL database, Firebase/Firestore and Firebase/Auth.

INK PRESSIVE

WEB DEVELOPER | INKPRESSIVESCREENPRINTING.COM

Oct 2020-Apr 2021

- Co-designed with another developer& built a full-stack website that is able to handle and integrate custom order submissions, upload designs, dynamically generated instagram post, public and private routes and authentication.
- The goal was to bring their company to the web where they can handle more clients and frequent inquiries about their business, and chose the featured instagram post.
- Technology: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Material-UI, noSQL database, Firebase/Firestore,
 FireBase/Auth.

LOCAL EVENTS APP

PERSONAL PROJECT | LOCALEVENTS.VERCEL.APP

May 2020-Present

- Created & and built full-stack website where users can create and update events details,
 upload event images add location details on google maps APIs. Features dynamically generated events using public and private routing and JWT authentication.
- The goal was to have an introduction in headless CMS, backend development and SQL databases, working to improve full-stack development.
- Technology: Next.JS, React, Context API, CSS, React-Bootstrap, Node.JS, Express, SQL/Postgres database, Strapi and JWT.

EDUCATION

MURRAY STATE UNIVERSITY

MAJORED IN ENGINEERING PHSYSICS

2012-2014

WEST KENTUCKY TECHNICAL AND COMMUNITY COLLEGE

ASSOCIATES IN MATHEMATICS

2014-2016

TOOLS

JavaScript	Red	ict JS	Next J	IS	Gatsby	/ JS	нти	ИL	CSS	SASS		JSX	В	Bootstrap
React Bootstrap		Material UI		Firebase		Stro	Strapi		de JS	Express	3	Git		GitHub
filemaker pro														

SKILL SET

Problem Solving	unicatio	n Re	sponsive Design	Mobile First Design			
Functional Program	ООР	ES6+	Async/Await	Rest API	Context API		
React-Hooks							